<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://adrybakov.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://adrybakov.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-11-04T11:49:21+00:00</updated><id>https://adrybakov.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>Personal card of Andrey Rybakov. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Russian-Ukrainian War</title><link href="https://adrybakov.github.io/blog/2023/russia-ukraine-war/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Russian-Ukrainian War"/><published>2023-10-08T18:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-10-08T18:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://adrybakov.github.io/blog/2023/russia-ukraine-war</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://adrybakov.github.io/blog/2023/russia-ukraine-war/"><![CDATA[<p>This site was not created as a platform for expressing of my political beliefs. It was intended for the presentation of my professional side. However, this text should and will be here.</p> <h3 id="in-english">In English:</h3> <p>On February 24, 2022 Russia invaded Ukraine. This act, this aggression, has led to the immeasurable grief and suffering for countless people. The government of my country is destroying the future and murdering people in a screaming atrocity, trying to drag us all into the hell of barbaric, pointless conflict.</p> <p>The war must stop. Russian army must withdraw from all occupied territories of Ukraine. Political prisoners and prisoners of war must be freed. The government of Russia is illegitimate and must be replaced. Those responsible for this war and for the crimes in it must face a trial and be held accountable for their actions. The damage to Ukraine must be compensated.</p> <p>Russia itself must undergo significant change. We cannot continue to live in a country ruled by shameless lies, fear and brutal force. Our future depends on the protection of individual rights and freedoms. The possibility of usurping state power must be eliminated. It does not seem achievable from today, but it must be done. Otherwise there will be always a threat of another war, of more suffering both to the people inside Russia and to its neighbors.</p> <p>Justice for Ukraine. Freedom for Russia.</p> <h3 id="in-russian">In Russian:</h3> <p>24 февраля 2022 года Россия вторглась в Украину. Эта агрессия, которая привела к неизмеримому горю и страданиям бесчисленного множества людей. Правительство моей страны уничтожает будущее и разрушает жизни в вопиющем зверстве, пытаясь втянуть нас всех в ад варварского, бессмысленного конфликта.</p> <p>Война должна прекратиться. Российская армия должна покинуть все оккупированные территории Украины. Политические заключенные и военнопленные должны быть освобождены. Правительство России нелегитимно и должно смениться. Все кто ответственен за эту войну и за совершенные на ней преступления, должны предстать перед судом и понести ответственност за свои действия. Ущерб Украине должен быть возмещен.</p> <p>Сама Россия должна измениться. Мы больше не можем быть страной, которой правят с помощью бесстыжей лжи, страха и жесткой силы. Наше будущее должно быть построено вокруг прав и свобод личности. Узурпация государственной власти должна быть исключена. Из сегодняшнего дня это кажется недостижимым, но это необходимо сделать. В противном случае всегда будет угроза новой войны, новых страданий, как для жителей России, так и для ее соседей.</p> <p>Справедливость для Украины. Свободу для России.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This site was not created as a platform for expressing of my political beliefs. It was intended for the presentation of my professional side. However, this text should and will be here.]]></summary></entry></feed>